A good session can be seen today, so the rest
we did a great write with Bishop, a
good opportunity to research this momentum today, the
structure is positive, yesterday Nifty
Bank showed leadership today, it is right,
keep ITR release his tox
on the radar for buying, but you should
not change the up of 16500, any retracement
goes, any indication of market cooling
off, then those will
become entry points, your devices are going left right now, it is
on your skin and Bank Nifty
tomorrow also, the structure of white performance
looks like a much better time,
preparation of the teacher of this point is
moving towards question updates, that is why Didi,
I want the notification which has come, please
share it in the Nirjan group, we have become
this authenticator internally, now the news,
this notification has come regarding oil gauge paste,
so these are important stocks
on the radar, upstream downstream, all the oil
companies, celery flower etc.
Inspector Saifuddin,
but if you fry something else beyond this, then the number one
market  And
actually the results are good,
where it was expected that it would remain limited, if we
look at the other side, we have seen an increase, the
figure of 1272 crores has been seen, the
profit has been seen
increasing since 10:30,
but the commentary is not that strong, we will keep an
eye on the mother as well and the company is
saying that pressure will be seen in matchsticks in the second quarter,
this time mother jeans will be under
pressure, 22.75 cents came and this is Lo, this
toothpaste, if you compare it with F-18, then the
daughter of F-18 has low margin,
after that this is the lowest that this company has offered today
and the election campaign is going on, the
management has clearly said that rural demand is
not picking up, compared to open, there was a
lot of strength in building construction in the last quarter also, Meena, there
was no demand in rural areas, demand still does
not appear to be increasing that much, the management has also
commented that efforts for demand draft recovery will be
awaited, so this is commentary,
but overall results may be seen enjoying more on good commentary,
Om K  Revenue growth is 40%,
much better than expected. Beauty and personal segments did not see
growth of up to 17%. It was
estimated that there would be an increase of 9 to 10, 20 to 11
%, so the
delivery is good, but the comments did
not improve. It was a false hope. On the
other hand, ICICI Lombard
saw a good increase in profits. An increase of up to 80% was
seen. A
profit of up to 350 crores was posted by the company. There has been an
increase of 30% in the premium. There has been a growth of 10% in the next pre-quarter.
Underwriting loss has reduced to 193 crores,
equivalent to 10 crores on a yearly basis. So, it has been a strong
quarter. Turmeric has been
seen coming from the company in the grocery minium, so
you have to keep that thing in mind. On the other hand,
Ambuja Cement's
performance is good. There has been an increase of up to 50% in profitability.
This is the 18th century in revenue. If
you think about the revenue, it is at 3393 crores. The
estimate was 30 to 25 crores, son.
Although some pressure has been seen at the level, the
figure of 0 crore has come out and a
decline of 29 cents has been seen at the last 29. Matchbox is
actually 17.1 chapters. In fact, the quarterly
inline has been done, you should definitely keep that in mind, the
numbers will remain relaxed on reference also. There was an
increase in profit, a profit of 2
crores in profit term profit,
where there is an increase in revenue, that
not much increase was seen, so you should keep in mind that in the
board meeting of Vedanta which was held yesterday, the
board has finally approved the dividend of 19.5 pips per share, so
positive for you and
interesting development is coming out from Grand, there is a lot of
news, Agrasen is saying
that they are preparing a b2b e-commerce platform
for building materials, where they will
invest up to two thousand crores
in 5 years and so that development is actually the
cost of flag in similar business and
they have done a lot of attractions
and it has become complete, so the kind of thing regarding that  The
response was received, the Home Secretary said that he
is in some business, why should we enter and
he will actually be seen making a big investment,
A's
paint, two paints